<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Package documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About Automic's NEXUS Package
================================

Nexus is a repository manager. It allows to proxy, collect, and manage software dependencies and makes it easy to distribute implemented software. With this package we automate the Sonatype Nexus services for the artifact that achieve the given business goal:
* Upload artifact
* Retrieve artifact

=ARA Compatibility=
This Nexus Package also offers cusotm types for all the Nexus actions which further can be used in ARA.

=Supported Nexus versions=
Following version of Nexus is supported:
* Sonatype Nexus 2.11.4

=Limitations=
(none)

=Setup=
* Oracle JDK 1.7 or higher must be installed on Agent OS and "java" must be set as executable on the same.

* The Agent should be able to access the Nexus URL(s) in order to make HTTP requests.

* Modify the HTTP timeout parameters as per your environment. By default "CONNECTION_TIMEOUT" is defined as 30000 and "READ_TIMEOUT" is defined as 60000. Both are defined in milliseconds. 0 means no timeout.

* You should have connection details to connect to Nexus Services.

* REST API(s) should be enabled for Nexus environment.

* If required, Anonymous access should be enabled for Nexus environment to run actions without username and password.

=Variables=
PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PRV.VARA.PACKAGE_PARAMETERS
* HTTP timeout parameters can be configured in this variable. Values are defined in milliseconds. 0 means no timeout.

=Actions=
Following actions are supported for Nexus.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.ACTION.UPLOAD_ARTIFACT
This action is used to upload the artifact to Nexus repository using GAV parameters i.e group, artifact, version paramters. A user can upload the artifact using the login credentials (login and password) or can upload anonymously if the user has the rights to upload. As this is an asynchronous operation, user needs to cross check if the artifact has been uploaded. The deployment of an artifact depends on the rights that has been permitted to the user for the Nexus repository. If the access setting for the repository is set to "disable redeploy", then user cannot deploy the same artifact again. If the access setting is set to "read-only", then the user cannot upload any artifact to the repository.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.ACTION.RETRIEVE_ARTIFACT
This action is used to retrieve an artifact from Nexus repository using GAV parameters i.e group, artifact, version parameters.

=INCLUDES=
* PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.INCLUDE.ATTACH_RESOURCE									
   Attach the nexus jar to current agent.It can be used for both Windows and Unix environment.
   
* PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.INCLUDE.BUILD_ACTION_SPECIFIC_JAVA_ARGUMENTS				
  This include is used to add action specific arguments to the string that is passed to the java command while caling the nexus jar.It can be used for both Windows and Unix environment.
  
* PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.INCLUDE.BUILD_JAVA_ARGUMENTS								
  This include is used add arguments which are common for all actions.This along with action specific arguments are passed to the java command while calling the nexus jar.It can be used for both    Windows and Unix environment.
  
* PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.INCLUDE.CHECK_JOBSTATUS									
  It calculates and publish the job status based on some known parameters. It considers the following things into account.
	* Any OS command failed or not. (E.g. ERRORLEVEL OS variable)
	* Job explicitly sets error code into known variable.  
	* AE Script processing error. (E.g. Validation errors)
	It considers any non zero value as error scenario.Further based on job status, it logs the success or failure message into Job report.
	This include can be only used in Job's Process tab.It can be used for both Windows and Unix environment.
  
* PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.INCLUDE.ECHO_ON_OFF										
 This include is used for echo ON or OFF 
  
* PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.INCLUDE.ESCAPE_ARG_VALUE									
  It escapes the Nexus input parameters and wrap the parameter surrounded by quotes(").It can be used for both Windows and Unix environment.
	
* PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.INCLUDE.LOAD_PCK_PARAMETERS								
  Load the package parameters from VARA object.It can be used for both Windows and Unix environment.
  
* PCK.AUTOMIC_NEXUS.PUB.INCLUDE.SET_EXEC_ENVIRONMENT								
  It sets general environmental variable(s) which can be further used in Jobs. It also changes the agent current directory to bin.
  This Include object can be used for both Windows and Unix environment as per the Agent]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>